// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is smallest unit of the information?",
    answer: "A bit",
    options: [
      "A bit",
      "	A byte",
      "	A block",
      "A nibble"
    	

    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is not an operating system?",
    answer: "Oracle",
    options: [
      "Windows",
      "Linux",
      "Oracle",
      "DOS"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "When was the first operating system developed?",
    answer: "1950",
    options: [
      "1948",
      "	1949",
      "1950",
      "	1951"
    ]
    
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What else is a command interpreter called?",
    answer: "shell",
    options: [
      "prompt",
      "	kernel",
      "shell",
      "command"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Banker's algorithm is used?",
    answer: "To prevent deadlock",
    options: [
      "To prevent deadlock",
      "To deadlock recovery",
      "To solve the deadlock",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which type of topology is best suited for large businesses and coordinate the operation of distributed  branch outlets?",
    answer: "Star",
    options: [
      "	Ring",
      "	Local area",
      "	Hierarchical",
      "Star"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "The location of a resource on the internet is given by its?",
    answer: "URL",
    options: [
      "	Protocol",
      "URL",
      "	E-mail address",
      "ICQ"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which software prevents the external access to a system?",
    answer: "Firewall",
    options: [
      "Firewall",
      "Gateway",
      "Router",
      "Virus checker"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The term FTP stands for?",
    answer: "File transfer protocol",
    options: [
      "File transfer program",
      "File transmission protocol",
      "File transfer protocol",
      "File transfer protection"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The term WAN stands for?",
    answer: "Wide Area Network",
    options: [
      "Wide Area Net",
      "Wide Access Network",
      "Wide Area Network",
      "Wide Access Net"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];